

# CONTACT

**:** +44 7580199079

: angelknela5@hotmail.co.uk

. https://www.linkedin.com/in/angel-canela

: https://github.com/angelknla

★: 28 Wilde House, Avenue Road, Acton, London. W3 8YR

## PERSONAL SKILLS

Communication
Ability to Work.
Decision Making 85%
Time Management
Conflict Resolution
Leadership 70%
Adaptability 80%

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

-	English 95%	-
-	Spanish	
-	Japanese 85%	-
-	Korean	_

# **ANGEL CANELA**

# Junior Full Stack Software Engineer

#### **PROFILE**

I am passionate about software engineering; I have recently finished my studies in software engineering, and have some experience working with computer systems, software architectures, data structures, UI wireframing, problem-solving algorithms and developing, front and back end, web-based applications. Furthermore, I have great programming skills and I excel at working with a variety of programming languages. (See skills section)

## **EDUCATION**

#### BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND MATHEMATICS.

The Open University 2017 - 2021. Grade: 1st

- Key modules: Computer systems, Software engineering, Problem Solving with Algorithms, Pure Mathematics, Java Programming, Data Structures.

#### BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING.

University of Oviedo 2007 - 2012. Grade 2:1

- Industrial and Mechanical Engineering studies.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **CABIN CREW**

Cathay Pacific Airways / London 2013- Till Date

My main role was to:

- To ensure safety, security and safety responsibilities are performed to the highest
- Ensure compliance with all company policies
- Be an ambassador of the Cathay Pacific brand.
- Create effective working relationships with colleagues to foster teamwork.
- Top 15% performance

#### JAPANESE TEACHER

Educatiò / Spain 2010- 2013

Undertaking full time job while still in university. One of my main roles was to teach Japanese to students from different backgrounds and develop business relationships with clients (students).

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Coding Languages:

- JAVA, JavaScript, HTML5/CSS3, XML, Python, C#,

Frameworks/Systems:

**React JS, Node JS, Express JS**, Bootstrap, jQuery, Visual Studio, Atom, IntelliJ IDEA, Android Studio, Git Version Control

Database Technologies:

- SQL databases such as MySQL, **PostgreSQL**. NoSQL databases such as **MongoDB** using frameworks like Mongoose.